<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
        <string name="changelog_text"><![CDATA[
<strong>You can view this again in the about screen.</strong>
<br></br>
<br></br>
<strong>1.5.2</strong>
<ul>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Option to join beta program. Please join if you would like to contribute to Chromer\'s development.</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVE:</b> Minor improvements to web heads snapping to trash and webhead physics.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Chromer getting disappeared from recents view.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Open in Chromer is shown in Chrome beta and dev versions. Now a separate Open in Chrome will be shown.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Crashes and minor bugs.</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.5.1</strong>
<ul>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Ability to choose color of web heads.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Ability to close all webheads from notification bar.</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVE:</b> Webheads dragging. Webheads now snap to trash when near.</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVE:</b> Scrolling behaviour in Chromer settings screen.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Not able to perform search on some keyboards. Now <b>search icon</b> will be shown on your keyboard, press that to launch URL or search.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Crash when trying to install Chrome from dialog.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Multiple crashes related to webheads.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> Chromer settings appearing randomly when closing custom tabs.</li>
    <li><b>FIX:</b> For 6.0+, re ask permission to draw on other apps if it was revoked with webheads turned on.</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.5</strong>
<ul>
    <li><b>NEW: WEBHEADS -</b> Ability to stack multiple links in floating bubbles and open them later. See the separate Intro in main screen.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Configurable action item in custom tab. Choose between secondary browser and any sharing app. <b>Example:</b> Choose <b>Pocket</b> to instantly save the link.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Ability to do text and voice search from main screen with the new material design search bar.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Dynamic toolbar enhanced. Now can adapt color based on the launching app\'s color.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Launch screen, new icon and app intro.</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Better app pickers</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Sharing a non url text to Chromer will now do a Google search. Also in text selection pop up in 6.0</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Setting default behaviour on Cyanogen devices</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Improved warm up and pre-fetch performance on non Chrome browsers</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Reduced memory consumptions and general crash fixes</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> UI layout changes</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.4.1</strong>
<ul>
    <li>Rewritten affected code to avoid potential license violations.</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.4</strong>
<ul>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Pre fetching. Chromer can scan links on screen and pre load them in background for you.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Option to keep browser warmed up. Improves launch times!</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Dynamic toolbar color. Chromer can provide color based on the website, if the website has it.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Secondary browser option. Quickly get to your preferred app.</li>
    <li><b>NEW:</b> Add to home screen option.</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> More material design</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Better setting default behaviour.</li>
    <li><b>IMPROVED:</b> Copy and share actions now target the current open page instead of first open page.</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.3</strong>
<ul>
   <li><b>DONATE option.</b> Please donate if you like this app and to support development:)</li>
   <li>Share links to open in Chromer</li>
   <li>For 6.0, select a text link to open in Chromer</li>
   <li>Option to choose between multiple Chrome versions</li>
   <li>About screen</li>
   <li>Link to Chromer G+ community</li>
   <li>Changelog screen</li>
   <li>Link to Chrome in case no custom tab provider is found</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.2.1</strong>
<ul>
   <li>Reworked share menu. Direct share enabled for 6.0</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.2</strong>
<ul>
   <li>Change Toolbar color to your liking</li>
   <li>Configure animations</li>
   <li>Link to read about chrome custom tabs</li>
   <li>Option to share Chromer link to others</li>
   <li>Licenses dialog</li>
   <li>Tutorial flow performance fixes</li>
   <li>Icons and imagery updated</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.1</strong>
<ul>
   <li>Much requested copy and share options</li>
</ul>
<br></br>
<strong>1.0</strong>
<ul>
   <li>Fixed "no custom tab compatible browser found" issue.</li>
</ul>
]]></string>
</resources>